Welcome back.
Welcome.
So, Raghu, tasked to create a social media app, so I know some might completed that task.
So in this video, I'm going to create my vision for it.
Let's create a new design while.
Okay, let's rename it.
So increasingly, I told you you can use like an iPhone frame or if you want to make a web application,
you can do that.
So for this project, I'm going to give it next door.
So let's first create a wire frame for it.
So in this section, we are going to have a groups like WhatsApp groups.
And in this situation, we are going to make personal messages.
And over here we are going to a chats.
So in this panel, we are going to have things like Home Chad setting the bell notification and the
power button.
Let's say the user is currently on the Charge six, and so the user will know from this bot, the user
will know he's in charge section.
OK, so this is going to be our group, so let's add some texture for you.
OK, so in this election, we are going to add a group, so let's take it over here.
And in this section, we are going to have a message from Postman's.
And over here, we are going to have like a message from a group or message from personal.
Much like Rachel.
I had a call button over here, and, uh, it's also earned a video call button.
OK, I'm less clear that that works going, OK, listen, the color of the.
And over here, we are going to add.
I'm Michael, for local, and in this section, we are going to have some charts.
OK, so remaining things like iron of paperclip.
So in groups, we are going to hell like the small groups.
Groups from like your school or other individual groups for friends.
OK, and also in the person's personal, you can get messages from your friends or your teacher or your
colleagues like that.
So this is going to be our world frame for this project.
So this is how my vision is going to look like.
So I know you might be done in a different way.
So I took inspiration from like WhatsApp and Discord from to application.
So in the next word, I'm going to design a UI for our social media app.
So that's me signing off.
Thanks for watching, and I will see you guys in the next one.