Welcome back, so impressively, we made this wireframe for our social media app.
So in this video, we are going to make the actual UI for that.
I think I have to remember the name this wire frame, so I will only this is the wire from.
OK, let's choose a frame that is going to be our next door and the rectangle on the and just to center
on this.
Is foreign.
OK, so you can see the all corners are sharp, so let's make them all around or chipped and select
them all.
Let's crank up to like 20.
Oh, sorry, I accidentally use this traditional tool.
I have to use the corner radius, so it is most frequently, OK.
There's the background color of this frame.
It's a bit gray.
Look, watch a little bit, and let's make them all a white.
Look at this and add a drop shadow.
OK, and it's in the color thing to like, which bluish.
So it totally depends on you which color you want to use.
So let's say for working on air and you don't know like what color to use, then you can use this website
called Color Hunt.
And in this website, you will get lots of color ballots like this one.
So for this project, I'm going to use this color palette.
So I really don't read it, so I'm going to just drag it on my figma project.
I think this one.
So let's try this one.
So for this section, I'm going to choose, say, this column.
It will argue like that this white.
OK.
And let's add a profile logo or you.
OK, now it is time to earn our icons like Go.
Let me see if I can.
We get like two of them, like this round on all this square one for this project.
I'm going to use this one.
So it totally depends on your office searching.
Setting and home also, we are on this call.
You.
Logo.
So for now, I'm important this icons or less and then one of my one.
So first of all, let's make them a little bit bigger.
So, you know, I use like 30 for.
So let's make it up to 40.
So it will look more better or more interesting.
I think I have to change the color of it, let's make it right.
OK, go to selection and let's make them light, so.
This is not selected, so that's my point.
OK, let's entertain one by one.
And now it is going to be over here.
You know, he's going to be asked to call.
And she's going to be.
Checked and sitting.
In this them.
Hold shift, select them all and R&amp;D center.
Alan, what is interesting this?
Let's and spacing.
OK, so our spacing also.
Oculus earned a profile.
Click on Go to ship to the image.
So let's chew like this property.
OK, let's place it on this logo.
You can see in this place now and also look perfect.
So this early stroke?
So we totally depends on you, if you want to add stroke, you can or you can live as it, it's like
this.
OK, one thing is something that so we are in currently jurisdiction, so it's clear that.
Rectangle.
You're listing the color of it.
I'm going to use this for it.
And to look at this one.
And listing the color of it into this one.
Let's bring that message sort of calling to front.
Click on it and link to front, are you going to use that right square bracket or shortcut?
OK, so if I like zoom out, you can see.
It looks.
OK, so user will know he's in this jurisdiction.
Like this?
OK, so let's make a group text audio.
OK, Alison, antiseptics, thanks.
Oh, sorry.
To six, I want to make one or so misspellings.
So let's change the font.
I like the font popping.
And let's make it bolt like this.
Now this act or groups.
Girls are too attached, so let's say this is the group from your college.
Let's make it a regular.
I heard a line audio.
OK.
The digital.
And is it?
Like this, and I think I'm going to change the color of it, and we'll make it a bit like a green.
OK.
Like this one?
So let's say someone dropped the message or something like.
Let's stick with the font size up to like four.
Like this?
Careless at the time.
So you will know when this message is delivered, what he got from someone.
A on 30.
At 8.30, he got a message from that group.
So let's change the.
OK, just make it up.
OK.
I think I may made up collecting.
And he told him.
Let's make it a group song because we are going to use this thing multiple times.
Press control to make them a group.
And this copy?
This stinks.
And I said just this ongoing episode like this, all of them, and it's legitimate upvotes like this,
and you can tune that time of it.
And also the name of their group as team.
This is like up to like seven point twenty one.
So let's copy this exactly the same thing on our personal section also.
All right.
You forgot to hold.
Like this?
OK, so first of all, listing the group name over here, let's say you have a list of all gamers.
And in the school group, nursing students.
So less added image on these two groups action subject to less image.
OK, so first one is the first images of our council, so I'm going to air this, imagine two cameras.
Second, when it's like students.
And let's say the imaginary students are programmers, so I'm glad were here.
So I think it does not make sense for this image, so I'm going to add over here.
So I think for Remercier to choose a different image.
Let's see our rumors out of the fan of Marvel saw him when I heard that Marvel image.
Let's say they are fired up like Loki, so soulless, add the look you make you look like this.
Let's say you edited the image, but the image is like not blessed very well, so you can double click
on it, go to film, select the image and you can choose a crop top and just that image.
Or you can like movies like this and cancel this one.
So.
The images placed now the message audio.
So I'm going to add some emojis.
I think in windows the shortcut is for images is Windows Plus or donkey?
So it will open the emoji panel audio so you can add emojis like this once again, as Anderson is saying.
I think this.
And over here, I'm going to parents and I'm like this.
So it totally depends on who you can like and do what you want.
So we are done with our group.
So let's say the name of this girl is the Rachel.
Like, I'm a big fan of like friends, so that's why I did this animal is ritual, so you can earn whatever
you want, even already wear name or next name, it totally depends on you.
And the last one is going to be childbirth.
So take a look at some random text.
OK, so I did some random text over you, so like I have written the time, and so I think the message
from Rachel at eight 46.
So let's add image audio.
People have told this image.
OK, so images blessed now.
So in this section, we are going to be checked as well as copy this one.
Or out on the water section.
OK, so you can see the problem here.
So I copied this group, but the group is not visible, so I have to text again.
And the simple rectangle.
Over here.
I understand the color of beetroot like this, but one.
And the concern is going to be 20.
So let's make it a little bit bigger.
So let's add, Rachel, over here.
What if I like drag it over here, it is going to be add back, so we have to bring this at front or
click on it and choose bring to front.
And now let's split it over here.
OK.
So we have to make some changes or here like this at a stroke.
It's made of quite.
This change to the point.
Also in the corner of the text is going to be white and also increase the font size on a saying up to
24.
And currently she's online.
And we have got him on this one.
The system on this line.
Looking forward to do so, we have to some some consortium that is going to be out on the call and will
be able to flex and dragged it over here and the color of this background is white and also the color
of their tyquan is white.
So it is not visible.
So let's bring it into front to front, and let's check it out here.
OK?
Forty.
And this visit here, and I think I also tracked video one.
OK, so this year.
This is bringing bring to front, OK, this island is rich and poor and working.
So it is, Orlando, you might see in that three minutes or so in icon, we don't have that many, so
we have to create it manually by using three ellipses.
So let's clear that.
It's clear to them and it's like this.
I think we have to make it a bit smaller, so connected to $11, maybe like a billion or eight.
OK, so we didn't know when all this audio, so first, let's make it look like I'm 20, so it is going
to be easier to move from one place to another.
OK, so Saturday morning is thanks to air jets.
So let's copy this one.
Oh, that's great.
I think I have undeclared Bennett.
There is no color on the color palette.
OK, so this gray color.
Done.
Let's make it smaller.
So let's create.
Might.
OK.
Like this.
Less important.
Mike Burton over here.
And I think I so forward that people like them.
What clip?
And the camera.
OK, so let's end with them.
I mean, first of all, let's.
Make it bigger like a collect call and also change the color of it.
Let's turn, let's make it.
Like this current.
OK, now we're going to.
Listed on this chart.
S..
Well, this is going to be here, and I think the bill is white and it's all here.
So they sense it first.
OK.
OK, let's align these things.
OK, so these things are Leno and early next door here.
Let type your message.
It's making it a bit bigger.
I think Connecticut is 14.
I think it is going to be fine.
OK, thank you.
Yes.
OK, so things are demeaning that only the so I search on the go to guard in this section.
What?
I don't find anything, so I'm going to add some random charts for you.
Let's say I recommended a game to a region.
Let's give the corner to the supply of 20 straight Polygon.
OK.
And just queue on the corner to disappear like, all right.
I think I have to change the color of it so that the color of which.
Okay, so.
So we just kind of look like this, or let's make a group of them so we can use it multiple times.
Or to select and control cheap.
The over here is arid text.
So let's make it simple.
And for 20, the difference on how we can use your other favorite font.
The center.
I think that it's like this on this mechanism, we're despondent.
So it has decreased the following sites a little bit smaller.
OK.
Like this, and we have to earn time.
So I'm going to copy this one folder and drag it over here.
So let's create another that section, I can copy this one, but.
But I want to do this Polygon do like a left side, so I have to create the new one.
That's why that's why I have to create a new one.
It's most in the cultural picture.
You can be like a guy with different color or you can like a.
Used to say one, so I'm going to disagree.
One.
And so the polygon.
So this is where I finished my social media project.
So I know it, you might get a different way or you took inspiration from different applications like
Facebook or Instagram.
So it totally depends on, you know, what just might look different or better than me.
So this isn't a single page application, so we are not going to use the prototype.
So if we had multiple pages like music apps, so.
So in that app, we had multiple pages, like four pages.
So that's why we connected those projects.
So this is a single page.
So this is how my social media app looks like.
So that's important, too, and I will see you guys in the next project.